

A proactive and self-motivated developer with years of full stack developing experience. I have proven ability and rich experience from multiple projects and work knowledge with both coding and DevOps. With my excellent time management skill, advance planing ability and solid leaning capability, I look forward to embracing my next career challenge.

SKILLS

• Front End:

Angular 6/7/8, TypeScript 3.x, JavaScript ES6/ES7/ES8, JQuery 3.x, RxJS 6, Node.js, AngularJS, ReactJS, Moment.js, npm, yarn, Webpack, Gulp, Babel, TSLint, ESLint, Popper.js, Select2, Malihu Scrollbar, HTML5, CSS3, SASS/LESS, Bootstrap 3/4, Angular Powered Bootstrap 4/5, Material Design Icons, Font Awesome Icons, Responsive Design

Front End Testing:

Jasmin, Karma, Protractor, TypoeMoq, html-dnd

GIS:

Mapbox GL JS, Turf, TileJSON, GeoJSON, GeoJSON.Net, Google Map API, Tippecanoe, GDAL, WMTS, ESRI, ArcGIS Online, MAXAR (DigitalGlobe), HERE, Azure Map, TomTom, OpenStreetMap etc.

• Back End:

C#, .NET Core 1/2, Entity Framework Core 1/2, JAVA (Java EE & Java SE), Json.NET, NuGet, YAML, Cron, Hangfire, JWT Token, Stripe, SendGrid, Autho, SOAP, WCF

Back End Testing:

FluentAssertions, NSubstitute, MSTest, TestStack.BDDffy

Cloud Services:

Azure Service Bus (Queue/Topic&Subscription), Azure Storage (Blob/Table/Queue), Azure VM, Azure App Services,

AWS S3, AWS EC2, AWS Route 53, AWS CloudFront, AWS Lambda, Google App Engine, Google Cloud Storage, Google Compute Engine, Cloudflare

Database:

Microsoft SQL Server 2016/2019, MySQL 5.7/8.0, Azure Cosmos DB, SQLite

Architectures:

Service Oriented Architecture (SOA), RESTful APIs, Microservices

Develops Tools & Platforms:

Azure DevOps (VSTS), Jira, GitHub, Azure Repos, GitLab, BitBucket, Postman, InVision, Trello

DevOps:

Azure Pipeline, Docker, Jenkins

Methodologies:

Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Test Driven Development, Behavior Driven Development

EXPERIENCE

AUG 2017 - NOW

FULL STACK DEVELOPER, GIS Intelli

- Re-designed and developed existing Gruntify API and web application and turned it into a highly scalable SaaS offering as one of 3 major full stack developers in a team of 10
- Implemented Gruntify RESTful API with .NET Core 2.2, Cosmos DB, Hangfire, NuGet, Azure Storage, Azure Service Bus, Auth0, JWT Token, Stripe, SendGrid, GeoJSON.Net, FluentAssertions, NSubstitute, MSTest and TestStack.BDDffy
- Developed Gruntify to support 100+ map sources from 15+ map providers
- Implemented Gruntify web application with Angular 6/7/8, TypeScript, RxJS, JQuery, TSLint, Popper.js, Select2, Malihu Scrollbar, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Mapbox GL JS, Jasmine, Karma, Protractor, TypeMoq, Bootstrap 4, Angular Powered Bootstrap 4/5 and Responsive Design
- Developed Gruntify background job project with .Net Core, JSON.Net, PdfWriter, Azure
 Service Bus to handle report generation request to export data to various formats
- Implemented and maintained the CI/CD for Gruntify projects with npm, Node.js, Gulp, Webpack, Azure Pipeline
- Followed Test Driven Development (TDD) approach and tested all Gruntify projects with E2E tests and unit tests
- Utilized Postman, Azure DevOps, Trello, InVision and interactive mockup to aid development, testing and documentation generation for Gruntify projects
- Designed and developed full Gruntimaps project from a simple prototype into a stable and scalable RESTful API Service with .Net Core, SQLite, Azure Storage, Azure Service Bus, Tippecanoe, GDAL, AWS S3, Google Cloud Storage. The project turns successful and became a crucial part of Gruntify with heavy daily usage
- Leaded the development of 2 Open Declare projects concurrently for 2 state government agencies Electoral Commission Queensland (ECQ) and Electoral Commission South Australia (ECSA) with .Net Core MVC, Microsoft SQL Server, Entity Framework Core, SOAP, HTML5, CSS3, JQuery and WCF data integration
- Experimented Machine Learning with Tensorflow, YOLO, Google App Engine, Google
 Compute Engine and Google ML Engine for fish species visual identification

MAY 2015 - AUG 2017

IT SUPPORT + DEVELOPER, BANK OF AUSTRALIA

- Provided IT support for Queensland wide bank operation
- Managed 40+ computers and network devices within 3 intranets in high standard
- Developed "Auto Logbook System" in C#/SQL which processed 2000+ customer information
 & provided critical business analysis
- Developed "Account Information Management System" in C# Windows Form with PdfWriter and Excel for human error reduction and work flow optimization
- Developed "Customer Queue Management System" with Python, Raspberry Pi and other network components to ensure an improved and unified customer experience

DEC 2013 - MAY 2015

WEB DEVELOPER, UMART ONLINE

- Maintained store website with PHP, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap 3, AWS EC2
- Developed warehouse management web application with role-based permission system for store internal control

PORTFOLIO

MAY 2019 - NOW

ACCOUNT OPENING WIZARD

Account opening wizard (http://boc-wizard.azurewebsites.net/) is project to transform bank account opening form into a dynamic online form system.

- Developed the front-end project with Angular 7/8, Select2, Moment.js, npm, yarn, Webpack, Gulp, Babel, TSLint, ESLint
- Developed the back-end RESTful API with .Net Core 2, Azure Blob Storage, JWT Token and Microsoft SQL Server
- Setup CI/CD Pipeline with Azure Pipelines and npm, webpack and Gulp

EDUCATION

2016 - 2019

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, QUEENSLAND UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

GPA: 6.8/7.0 AVG: 90/100

Achievements:

- 2-year full HD (95% avg) while full time studying and full time working
- Nominated as Peer Learning Facilitator every year

2012 - 2013

MASTER OF ENGINEERING, UNIVERSITY OF NEW SOUTH WALES

GPA: 6.1/7.0 AVG: 83/100

2006 - 2016

B.S. IN ENGINEERING, TSINGHUA UNIVERSITY

REFEREE

Referee available upon request